(In Korean) You wanna die?
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir! Sir!
I'm sorry!
- I'm sorry.
- What are you doing?
[GASPS]
I'm sorry, sir.
Uh, sir?
My shoes, please?
(In Korean) Stupid!
Stupid? Me?!
You're the stupid one!
My shoes!
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- Wait-- Sir!
Sir!
[HANNAH] Sir, the shoes!
What are you doing here?
I just told you to get
the guest's clothes,
not wear them!
Take it off! We don't want
the guest to get your scabies!
What scabies, ma'am?
I don't have scabies.
We have the same healthy skin,
don't you think?
Thanks to the hotel AC.
I'm sorry about that.
I was carrying so much stuff,
so I wore some
so it'd get a bit lighter.
But I was on my way, I'm just--
Hush!
Stop with the excuses.
Take it off
before the guest sees you!
And you,
get the rest of the clothes.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Hurry up now!
My god!
What's wrong with my staff?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Who are you calling stupid?
Bye!
[SIGHS]
Fighting!